1st grade student, 10 years old, can you name your high school?
1年生10歳 高校名とか言える?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘じゃない?
Sakura...High school name Oh, that's right.
桜...高校名 あ、そうなんだ
It's true.
本当なんだ
1 year?
1年?
How old is a first year student?
1年生 ってことは何歳なの?
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
You're young.
若いね
I would be happy if he was too young.
若い子すぎたら嬉しい
Well then, just out of curiosity.
じゃあさ、興味本位なんだけどさ、
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
Do you do any fun club activities?
楽しい 部活とかでやってたりするの?
Club activities... Don't you have a basketball club?
部活...バスケ部やってない?
It's the basketball club.
バスケ部なんだ
Is basketball fun?
バスケ楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいね
Since when have you been playing basketball?
いつ からやってるのバスケは?
From high school to recently.
高校から 最近なんだ
Recently.
最近です
Can I film it?
映していいですか?
face.
顔
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いですよね
Well then, it's starting to rain.
じゃあ ちょっと、雨降ってきたから
Maybe it's the rain man.
雨おとこかもしれない
Shall we go inside for a moment?
ちょっと中入りましょうか
Shall we go inside?
中入ろうか
Nice to meet you again.
改めまして
This is Yuka-chan.
ゆかちゃんです
yes.
はい
lol Your face is cute.
笑 顔可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You're really young, really.
めちゃめちゃ若いよね、本当に
Well, that's what I'm most concerned about.
で さ、一番気になってるんだけどさ、
It's on the back of Twitter, next to the at sign.
Twitterの裏側にさ、 アットマークの横にさ、
It's written like JK1, but...
JK1みたいにさ、書いてるんだけどさ、
What is that?
あれって何?
TRUE?
本当?
It's true.
本当です
TRUE?
本当?
It's true.
本当です
No, there are quite a lot.
いや、結構多いんですよ
It's not a scam though.
詐欺じゃないけどさ
A lot.
多くて
Really, 1?
本当に、1?
1st year student, 16 years old.
1年生、16歳
Can you tell me the name of your high school?
高校名とか言える?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘じゃない?
Sakurahigashi High School.
桜東高校です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's true.
本当なんだ
1 year?
1年?
I'm a first year student.
1年生です
So how old are you?
ってことは何歳なの?
15 years old.
15歳
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
You're young.
若いね
You young people are amazing, I'm so happy.
若い子すげえな、嬉しいです
Well then, just out of curiosity.
じゃあさ、興味本位なんだけどさ、
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
fun.
楽しい
Do you do any club activities?
部活とかでやってたりするの?
Don't you have a club or basketball club?
部活、バスケ部やってない?
It's the basketball club.
バスケ部なんだ
Is basketball fun?
バスケ楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいです
Since when have you been playing basketball?
いつからやってるの、バスケを?
From high school.
高校から
It's been recent.
最近なんだ
Recently.
最近です
Is it hard to practice?
練習大変?
It's really hard.
めっちゃ大変です
That's right.
そうなんだ
What do you do in your free time?
休み時間とか何してるの?
I'm having a candy party with my friends.
友達とお菓子パーティしてます
Sweets party?
お菓子パーティ?
cute.
かわいい
Can we all bring some sweets?
みんなでお菓子持ち寄って?
that's right.
そうです
Are you going to eat sweets?
お菓子食べるんだ?
Eat.
食べます
Silently?
無言で?
No, I want something like Koibana.
いや、恋花とかしたい
Love flowers?
恋 花?
I'm going to fall in love with you.
恋花するんだ
Looks like a JK.
JKっぽいね
Does that mean you have a boyfriend now?
ってことは今、彼氏とかいるの?
No, my boyfriend.
いや、彼氏は
Is there someone you like?
好きな人いる?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
Are you there?
いるの?
No, yeah.
いや、うん
He's a senior on the soccer club, but he's a light player.
なんか、サッカー部の先輩とか、軽盤だけど
Well, that's right.
まあ、そうなんだ
Eh, I can't help it.
え、なんかやけるな
That's nice.
いいな
That's right.
そうなんだ
So, what are you doing in law?
じゃあ、法学とか何してるの?
Japanese, karaoke.
国語、カラオケ
karaoke?
カラオケ?
karaoke.
カラオケ
I have an image of JK going to karaoke.
なんかイメージあるね、JKってカラオケに
Are there any subjects you're good at?
なんか、得意な科目とかあるの?
Like studying.
勉強とか
My favorite subject, ah, Japanese, I'm good at it.
得意な科目、あ、国語、得意
I'm good at this.
ここ、得意なんだ
Japanese, good at it.
国語、得意
It's the Japanese language.
国語なんだ
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Yes, I do.
うん、してます
Well, I contacted you on Twitter today.
じゃあさ、今日ツイッターで連絡したんだけどさ、
It felt like I was recruiting,
なんか、募集って感じだったからさ、
Do you usually do a lot?
普段結構やってんの?
That's what it is.
そういうこと
It may be rude though.
失礼かもしれないけど
Usually.
普段は
Haven't you done it?
やってないの?
Usually, I don't do anything in particular.
普段は、なんか特に、やってなくて
by chance?
たまたま?
accidental?
偶然?
today?
今日?
Ah, coincidence.
あ、偶然
lucky.
ラッキー
Why is it like that today?
なんで今日はあれなの?
Oh, my mobile phone has been a little weird this month.
あ、携帯台がちょっと、今月やばくて
Oh, a mobile stand?
あ、携帯台?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
What, don't you have a part-time job?
え、バイトとかしてない?
Ah, no, now.
あ、いや、しては、今
Oh, are you doing that?
あ、してるの?
I'm growing.
成長してます
What kind of system are you doing?
何系してるの?
Oh, I work in the food and beverage industry.
あ、飲食系やってて
飲食系?
where?
どこ?
Acrylic up.
アクリルアップ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
He's a high school student.
高校生だね
But is the hourly wage low?
でも、時給低いか
that's right.
そうです
Eh, but even though it's cheap, you can still pay for a mobile phone, right?
え、でも、低いとはいえさ、携帯台くらい払えるでしょ?
Oh, no...
あ、いや...
Game maker.
ゲームの派金師
It's amazing.
す げちゃって
It's now.
今時だね
What game are you playing?
何のゲームやってるの?
that...
あの...
Ah, there's a guy who often does commercials.
あ、なんかよくCMやってるやつが、
Isn't that the one from that rhythm game?
あのリズムゲームのやつでしょ?
that's right.
そうです
Did you spin the gacha?
ガチャ回しちゃった?
A lot.
だいぶ
I see.
そっか
That's kind of urgently needed.
それはちょっと急遽必要だね
yes.
はい
Well, I don't usually do this, but today is a little crazy this month.
じゃあ、普段はやってないけど、今日ちょっと今月ちょっとやばい
It feels like it's a sudden thing.
から って感じで、急遽って感じだね
that's right.
そうです
Well, I'm kind of happy.
えー、なんか嬉しい
It was lucky, lucky.
ラッキーラッキーだったね
Well then, there's something I'd like to talk about here.
じゃあさ、ここちょっと話したいのもあるしさ、
Well, let's move a little.
なんだからさ、ちょっと移動しようか
Shall we go now?
そろそろ行こうか
You get it.
わかるよね
Well, let's go.
じゃあ、行こうか
yes.
はい
You came to the hotel.
ホ テ ル来ちゃったね
I can't go.
行けないね
You're a high school student, right?
高校生だよね
Come to the hotel.
ホテル来ちゃって
Yeah.
うん
Do you come often?
よく来るの?
No, it's not.
いや、じゃない
It just so happens that this is for hats.
これ帽子用とかもたまたまなんだもんね
that's right.
そうです
This is it.
これね
Pat me on the head because it's cute.
可愛いから頭なで
What did you do?
なしたの?
I did it.
なした
Are you nervous?
緊張しちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
Come on, I can't take it anymore.
ちょっとさ、もう我慢できないからさ、
Can I do what you said on Twitter?
ツイッターでさ、言ってたことをしてもらってもいい?
Ah, but it's still spinning.
あ、 でもまだ回ってたりします
Yeah.
うん
It's spinning.
回してるよ
I wish the camera would just stop.
カメラちょっと流石に止めてほしくて
But you said it was fine just now.
でもさっきいいって言ったじゃん
No, but I'm afraid of it leaking.
いや、でも流出とか怖いから
No, it won't leak.
いや、流出しないよ、だって
It's just me.
俺だけだよ
No, but I stopped the camera.
いや、でもさすがにカメラ止めてます
That's it.
だ って
Is it that scary?
そんなに怖い?
No, hmm.
いや、うーん
Don't trust me?
信用できない?
I agree.
そうですね
That's right.
そっかそっか
Well then, as I said earlier,
じゃあさ、さっきも言ってたけどさ、
Because the allowance will be increased compared to the original one,
元々のあれより手当て増やすから、
I think you said you were in 2nd place at first.
最初2位って言ってたと思うけど、
Increase by 1. Here you go.
1増やしてさ、ほら、ピッて
Because it's a promise, because I said it earlier,
約束だから、さっき言ってたから、
Well, yes.
さ、はい
It's good that it's gone.
しまったってことはいいってことだ
Well, that's good.
まあ、いいよね
Well, come down here.
じゃあ、ここ下に来て
Well then, let me take a camera.
じゃあ、ちょっとカメラ撮らせて
I've touched it quite a bit.
結構触ったことあるね
No, no, no, no.
いや、ない、ない、ない
It's getting hot.
熱くなってる
I like young girls, like JK.
JKとかさ、若い子好きなの、好きなの
I think I fell in love a little.
ちょっと恋をしたみたいだけど
Are you pulling?
引いてる?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Well then, take a look.
じゃあ、見てやって
You can see it hidden in your hand.
手に隠して見えるでしょ
Just touch it.
触るのはちょっと
why?
なんで?
No, just touch it.
いや、 ちょっと 触るだけじゃん
no,
いや、
I mean stop it.
止 めっていうか
what up?
どうした?
No, it's a little different from what I promised, I didn't say I'd touch it.
いや、約束と、ちょっと違う、触るのは言ってなかった
Didn't you say that?
言ってなかった?
I didn't say that.
言ってなかった
I wanted to touch it, my brain went straight to it, and I wondered what it would be like.
触りたくてさ、脳がすぐ行くし、どうかなと思って
No, but.
いや、でも
a little bit
ちょっと
Just let me touch you.
だけ 触らせて
Hey, just a little bit, just a little bit.
ほら、ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけ
Let me touch you.
触らせてよ
That leg hurts a little.
そこのちょっと、足痛いでしょ
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
Just let me touch you just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけ触らせてよ
I'm touching it.
触っちゃってるし
If you let me touch it, I'll add it again.
触らせてくれたら、またプラスしちゃう
I don't trust you.
信用ないよ
Plus, I don't trust it.
プラスすると信用ないよ
I'm still a little scared.
まだちょっと怖い
I see.
そっか
Well then, let's calm down.
じゃあさ、精神落としとくよ
Take it, take it.
受け取って、受け取って
Okay then, right?
じゃあいいでしょ?
It's hard to find anything like this.
なかなかないよ、こんな
About age...
歳...くらい
Are you still on your way to your first trip?
まだ初行く途中?
Yeah.
うん
I'm already a first year high school student.
もう高一だもんね
It's still to come.
まだ、これからだよ
Since when have you been wearing a bra?
いつからブラとかつけてんの?
Elementary school students.
小学生
Over your clothes.
服の上からって
You didn't say over your clothes.
服の上からって言ってないでしょ
I didn't say over clothes.
服の上からって言ってない
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I said.
って言ったけど
That's good.
いいよね
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I said and received the money.
って言ってお金を受け取ってたから
I think you said earlier that it was over your clothes.
服の上からってさっき言ってた気が
I didn't say it, I didn't say it.
言ってない、言ってない
I didn't say that.
言ってない
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
Ask me.
って聞いて
You didn't say over your clothes.
服の上からって言ってないでしょ
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I heard.
って聞いたんだよ
Are your friends doing this?
友達とかもさ、こういうことしてんの?
No, I don't really know.
いや、ちょっとわかんないかな
That...
そっちは...
why?
なんで?
Okay, just lie here for a while.
いいじゃん、ちょっとここ寝転んで
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I heard.
って聞いたんだから
I haven't heard of touching that part.
そこは触るって聞いてない
Did I just say no?
俺さっき断言した?
Just my chest.
胸だけって
No, no.
いや、やだ
You didn't say that.
言ってないでしょ
What do you want to do?
どうしたい?
Hey, it's coming out.
おい、出てるじゃん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Those who feel it quite a bit.
結構感じる方
Because I don't know.
わかんないからさ
Don't take it off.
脱がさない
Well, just take them off and look at your panties.
じゃあ、脱がしてパンツ見るだけ
Just touch it from above your pants.
パンツの上から触るだけ
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what I said.
って言ったじゃん
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
That's what you said.
って言ってたでしょ
Don't take it off.
脱がすな
I'm touching you from above my pants.
パンツの上から触るんだよ
I said it.
言ったじゃん
That's a different story, isn't it?
話違うでしょ、それは
Don't take it off.
脱がすな
Don't want to take off your bottom?
下は脱ぎたくない?
Take off your top.
上を脱げて
So, can you take off your top?
じゃあ、上を脱げる?
Now, let's take off the top.
じゃあ、上を脱ごう
Take off your top.
上 を 脱 ご う
Here, hurray.
ほら、万歳
I didn't say take it off.
脱ぐとは言ってないから
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Well then, yes.
じゃあさ、はい
Now, show me your underwear.
これで、下着姿になって見せて
Please accept it.
受け取ってね
You want it, right?
欲しいんでしょ
I want to help you.
助けてあげたいんだよ
It's going to be a lot of money to pay this month.
今月結構支払いやばいんでしょ
I'll give you that.
それあげるからさ
I'll give it to you, so let's take off your clothes and put on your underwear.
あげるから、 服脱いで、 下着姿になってみよう
It's not like we're sharing it.
別に共用してるわけじゃないからね
I just want to help with the money.
お金、協力してあげたいだけだから
Well then, let's stand there.
じゃあ、そこに立ってみようか
You can't see it, can you?
見えないでしょ
I'd like my money back.
お金返してもらおうよさ
Yeah.
うん
Hands, look, hands.
手、ほら、手
You're young.
若いね
It's chewy.
もちもちしてるね
Well, let's sit down again.
じゃあ、もう一回座ろうか
nice.
いいね
Melt it, melt it.
とけて、とけて
It's embarrassing to be touched.
触られるの、恥ずかしいの
That's right
そっ
mosquito.
か
You said you were going to touch it at the beginning.
触 るの、最初に言ってたでしょ
Come to the front,
手前に来て、
Leaning there, I drew my feet back,
そ こにもたりかかってさ、 足引っ向けて、
M-shaped recovery is not possible.
M字回復できない
It's still beautiful.
まだ、綺麗だね
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
hand
手
It's embarrassing to leave it behind.
を 置いといて、恥ずかしいのって
If you touch it, it will make a sound.
触ったら声出てるね
He's been quite enthusiastic about it several times, isn't he?
何回かや、結構乗り気だって、そうでしょ
That's right.
そんなもんね
That may not be the case.
そんなことはないかも
Isn't that so?
そうでしょ
I'll be waiting.
待ってるからさ
Hey, not directly.
ちょ、直接は
why?
なんで?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
No, directly inside the clothes.
いや、直接は、服の中
I didn't say it, I didn't say it.
言ってない、言ってない
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
At first, it was a different story.
最初、違う話だったから
It's time to hand over the money.
もう、お金渡した時
No, but it's inside the clothes.
いや、でも、それは服の中
First, can I touch you?
最初に、触っていい?
I'm touching something right now.
今、なんか触ってるんだよ
From there, inside your clothes.
そっから、服の中
I'm giving it to you separately.
別に渡してるんだよ
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
First, over your clothes.
最初、服の上から
Don't you want money?
お金欲しくないの?
No, money.
いや、お金は
If this happened, you want it, right?
もし、これで起きたってことは、欲しいんでしょ?
No, well.
いや、まあ
It's me.
私だもんね
I haven't heard of you taking off your underwear.
下着取るのは、ちょっと聞いてない
Didn't I tell you to take off your underwear?
下着取るのは、言ってない?
We're together, right?
一緒でしょ?
The clothes are the same, right?
服も一緒でしょ?
We're together, right?
一緒でしょ?
No, as expected.
いや、さすがに
No, as expected, underwear.
いや、さすがに、下着は
Do you want your money back?
お金返す?
Well then.
じゃあ
No, that's a bit.
いや、それは、ちょっと
Isn't that so?
そうでしょ
Have fun.
楽しまして
It makes me laugh.
笑っちゃうよ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Really enjoy it.
ほんと、楽しましてよ
It's a big deal.
せっかくなんだよ
I'll have you fuck me with your hands and mouth, but did you add money?
手と口で、ポンしてもらうけど、 お金プラスしたの?
But did you add it?
でも、 プ ラスしたの?
Yeah, I said touch it.
うん、触るって言ってたよ
I said touch it.
触るって言ってたよ
I added money, so that's about it.
お金プラスしたんだからさ、 そういう分ぐらい、
Wouldn't it be nice to have a little fun?
ちょっと楽しましてくれてもいいんじゃない?
But will you give it back?
でも、その返す?
No, that's a bit.
いや、それは、ちょっと
You don't like it, right?
嫌いでしょ?
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てさ
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
Just a little more, okay?
もうちょっと、いいでしょ?
About a little more.
もうちょっとぐらい
No, but that's different from the beginning.
いや、でも、 最初と話違うよ
That's why I said it.
だから、言ったじゃん
I told you all sorts of things, like you can touch me.
触っていいとかさ、いろいろ言ったじゃん
Yeah.
うん
Did you receive the money?
お金受け取ったんでしょ?
It's difficult though.
難しいのもあるけどさ
Turn it.
手回して
Is it visible?
映ってる?
Are you waiting for the camera?
カメラに自分待ちくるの?
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗だね
Lend me your legs and your hands for a moment.
ちょっと 足、両手貸して
Yeah.
うん
Lend me your hands.
両手貸して
Do a little bit in both hands.
両手にちょっとさ、やって
In between.
挟んで
If you let me live with this, I'll be done with it.
これで生かしてくれたら、もう終わりにいいよ
Ah, that's no good.
あ、駄目じゃん
This is no good.
これでいけない
Because I can't.
いけないから
Come on, it's still hurting here,
ちょっとさ、ここさ、まだ痛いからさ、
There are four pieces here once.
一回ここにさ、4つの枚なんで
Huh?
えっ
A little over here from the left side
左側から、ちょっとこっち
To.
に
Okay.
よ いしょ
You can't see it, can you?
見えないでしょ
There's still a little more to come.
まだもう少し付きなし
Well then, let's take this off for a moment.
じゃあ、ちょっとこれ脱いちゃおう
Didn't I tell you to take off your underwear?
下着脱ぐの言ってない?
Don't take your top off.
上脱いでんじゃん
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
yeah?
ん?
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
One more time.
もう一回
But hey, take your top off.
でもさ、上脱いでんじゃん
It's good here too, right?
ここもいいってことでしょ
It's coming off.
脱げてんじゃん
picture?
え?
I'm pulling the strings.
糸引いてるよ
That's naughty.
エッチだね
結構
Actually, I feel like I'm stuffy.
実はムッツリみたいな
show me.
見せて
Over there.
そこの
no.
いや
Shall I put it in there?
入れようか、そこに
Yeah, a little bit.
そう、ちょっと
Get out?
抜け取る?
I want it.
欲しいんだ
Get out?
抜け取る?
Well, it's no good if you don't show it.
じゃあ、見せないとダメだよ
Push it open.
押し開いて
Make sure you can see it properly.
ちゃんと見えるようにして
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Have you never grown up there?
そこ生えたことないの?
Will it not grow?
生えないか
Come on, it's you.
生えさろ、お前か
Well then, I can't see it properly yet,
じゃあさ、そこまだちゃんと見えてないから、
Try opening it.
開いてみして
picture?
え?
lie?
うそ?
Did you give the money?
お金渡したの?
Did you give it to him?
渡したでしょ?
Because that's what I want to see.
そこを見たいってことだからさ
Do it yourself, put your hands under your feet.
自分でさ、足の下から手回してさ
It's pink.
ピンクだね
Have you seen it yourself?
自分で見たことある?
do not have.
ない
Would you like to take a look?
見てみる?
Stop it.
やめて
It's wet.
濡れてるね
It's fine without it.
無しいいよ
Isn't it already inside?
もう入んじゃない?
refer to.
指
I'll put it in.
入れるの
Look.
ほら
What I put in won't come in.
入れたの入んないでしょ
It's wet.
濡れてる
It's tough.
きついね
Stop it.
やめて
Peast.
ピーストして
Is your pet here?
ペットいこっか
I had a pet once.
一 回ペットいこ
Lie down.
寝転んで
I'll put it in.
入れちゃうわ
It's a bit obvious to include it.
入れるのはちょっとさすがに
why?
なんで?
When you get this far, put it in.
ここまで来たら入れさして
It's a bit obvious to include it.
入れるのはちょっとさすがに
Why why?
なんでなんで?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
At first, I said “Petit”.
最初プチって
Well, that's true.
まあ、そうだけど
We're each other's noses.
お互いさ、お互い鼻からしてさ
It makes me want to sleep.
寝たくなるじゃん
My voice was coming out.
声出てたし
See you then.
じゃあさ
Should I add money?
お金プラスしたらいい?
Also.
また
Can I come in?
入れていい?
Come talk.
喋ってこむ
Does that mean I should wear rubber?
ゴムつけたらいいってこと?
It's a little raw as expected.
生はさすがにちょっと
Does that mean I should wear rubber?
ゴムつけたらいいってこと?
Which is better, rubber or raw?
ゴムか生どっちがいい?
It's rubber.
それはゴム
Does that mean I can put it in if I put on a rubber band?
ゴムつけたら入れていいってこと?
I'll make it shorter.
時間短めにするから
If so, it's petit.
だったらプチでしょ
I'll save you time.
時間プチにするから
That would be fine.
だったらいいでしょ
It's because I'm saving my time.
時間プチにするんだからさ
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
I also want to make more money.
お金も増やそうと
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
I'll put it in then.
じゃあ入れるよ
Should I wear rubber?
ゴムつけたらいい?
Then put on the rubber.
じゃあゴムつけて
Wait a moment, I'll go get it.
取ってくるからちょっと待ってて
Because I said okay.
いいって言ったからね
Can I put it on?
つけれる?
Have you ever worn it?
つけたことある?
It doesn't work at all.
全然つかないじゃん
endure, endure.
耐える耐える
It won't work.
つかないじゃん
This is no good.
だめだよこれ
No, look.
だめだよほら
It's ruined.
だめになったじゃん
I won't wear this.
つけないよこれ
I can't put it on.
つけないじゃん
Make it raw?
生にする?
Make it raw.
生にする
No?
だめ?
Because I got it.
取 ってきたから
Before I put it on.
つける前にさ
Give it a little squeeze with your hands.
手でちょっとしごいてさ
Stiffly stiffly.
ガッチリガチリして
Got it?
ついた?
I arrived.
ついた
Even rubber is fine.
ゴムだっていいんだよね
Because I put it on.
つけたから
I said okay
いいって言ったから
hey.
ね
I told you to put on a rubber band.
ゴ ムつけたらいいって言ったからね
Open your hands.
手を開けて
It's on.
ついてるよ
lie?
うそ?
what up?
どうした?
Suddenly.
急に
what up?
どうした?
Suddenly.
急に
It's on, right?
ついてるでしょ
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
It feels good, so it's okay.
気持ちいいからいいでしょ
Look.
ほ ら
It's louder than before.
さっきより声出てんじゃん
Get on your elbows.
ひじついてひじついて
It's louder than before.
さっきより声出てんじゃん
Then just bend your upper body.
じゃあ上半身だけ倒して
Put it in from the top.
上から入れてくんね
Put it in from above.
上から入れて
Because I'm going to lie down.
寝転ぶからさ
Come on up.
上に来て
Okay.
よ い しょ
Look.
ほ ら
I'll start from the top as soon as possible.
早く早く上から行くから
Let's go fast and do that grind.
早く行こうしてそのグラインドとかして
Touch my neck.
首とか触ってよ
I feel like I'm about to come out.
出ちゃいそうになるね
Take it outside.
外に出して
So just once, raise your legs, raise your hands,
じゃあ一回さ、足上げてさ、手をさ、
Can you put it between my legs?
俺の足の間に入れる?
Now move.
これで動いて
Take it outside.
外に出して
Because you say it's not enough anymore.
もう物足りないって言うから
It's been a while since I've been here.
俺もう久々するからさ
Can I try it again?
もう一回やっていい?
Is it one more time?
もう一回ですか?
Because it's a plus.
プラスするから
I don't have much left at the moment, but I'll take it down later.
今ちょっと手持ち少ないけどさ、後で下ろすからさ
For now, I'll just save this for once.
とりあえずこれだけ一回取っておいてさ
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Shall we do it again?
もう 一回やる?
Well, not once or twice.
まぁ一回も二回もね
Eh, but...
え、でも...
See you soon.
ちょっとまた
That's enough.
もういいじゃん
it is...
それは...
Only one together.
1個だけ一緒に
It's my second shot, so just a little.
2発目だからさ、ちょっと
Wait, wait, wait.
待って待って待って
picture?
え?